<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FantasyCostco</string>
    <string name="button_label_start">Shop!</string>
    <string name="description_background">Erroneous, non-Fantasy-Costco TAZ scene</string>


    <string-array name="item_names">
        <item name="rusted_can_of_cheerwine">Rusted Can of Cheerwine</item>
        <item name="virtuosos_mask">Virtuoso\'s Mask</item>
        <item name="throwing_shield">Throwing Shield</item>
        <item name="alchemists_ring">Alchemist\’s Ring</item>
        <item name="healing_potion">Healing Potion</item>
        <item name="haunted_doll">Haunted Doll</item>
        <item name="shield_of_heroic_memories">Shield of Heroic Memories</item>
        <item name="the_anti_gravity_sphere">The Anti Gravity Sphere</item>
        <item name="the_gluttons_fork">The Glutton\'s Fork</item>
        <item name="the_champions_belt">Champion\'s Belt</item>
        <item name="phone_a_friend_scrying_bones">Phone-A-Friend Scrying Bones</item>
        <item name="the_nit_picker">The Nit Picker</item>
        <item name="plastic_sheriff_badge">Plastic Sheriff Badge</item>
        <item name="flaming_poisoning_raging_sword_of_doom">Flaming Poisoning Raging Sword of Doom</item>
        <item name="no_sodium_salt_shaker">No-Sodium Salt Shaker</item>
        <item name="the_immovable_rod">The Immovable Rod</item>
        <item name="diadem_of_fabulous_truthiness">Diadem of Fabulous Truthiness</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="item_details">
        <item name="rusted_can_of_cheerwine">Has seen some shit, but seems to be radiating with vital energies. Grants +5 max HP. (400 GP)</item>
        <item name="virtuosos_mask"> Allows you to cast Disguise Self as a Cantrip instead of a 1st Level Spell. (1100 GP)</item>
        <item name="throwing_shield">Confers the same AC bonus as a regular shield, and can be used as a thrown weapon. Can travel IN A STRAIGHT LINE up to 30 feet, and deals 1d8 + STR/Prof. Damage. IT DOESN\’T COME BACK TO YOU AFTERWARDS. AND DON\’T TRY TO RICOCHET THIS SHIT. (1200 GP)</item>
        <item name="alchemists_ring">When the wearer of this ring imbibes a healing potion, they receive 1d6 additional healing.(500gp)</item>
        <item name="healing_potion">When the wearer of this ring imbibes a healing potion, they receive 1d6 additional healing.(500gp)</item>
        <item name="haunted_doll">This doll is very creepy. If its owner ever fails a third death save, the doll will take the hit instead, and will die in place of its owner.(100gp)</item>
        <item name="shield_of_heroic_memories">This perfectly round silver shield initially has a mirror finish. As a hero takes it into battle it remembers the enemies encountered, gaining a +1 to AC on any subsequent battle with creatures of that type. The events of the battle are intricately engraved onto the shield’s surface (which has a seemingly endless capacity for detail).

            The bearer of the shield may also attempt to recount past battles (real or imagined) to the shield. Upon a DC 10 charisma check or DC 15 bluff check, the shield confers a +1 AC against the creatures described in the tall tales.

            3 failed attempts at recounting stories cause the shield to be cleared of all of its memories. The engravings disappear. It reverts to its mirror finish. All bonuses are lost. (1200gp)</item>
        <item name="the_anti_gravity_sphere">a small fist-sized glass ball filled with a silvery smoke. When the sphere is destroyed, it disables the effect of gravity on everything in a 30ft radius. (500 GP)</item>
        <item name="the_gluttons_fork">Once a day this fork will allow the user to eat any non-magical item they can fit in their mouth and gain 2d6 points of health. Just tap the fork on the item and it will turn edible. (750 GP)</item>
        <item name="the_champions_belt">This ornate belt is given to someone who has bested all opponents in a test of strength.  Once per day the wearer may substitute their Strength score for their Wisdom or Charisma when making a stat check. (800 GP)</item>
        <item name="phone_a_friend_scrying_bones">Once per day, can be used to ask a yes, no, or maybe question to the fates (DM). There are three bones carved into people with happy faces and sad faces. All happy faces means yes, all sad faces mean no, anything in between means maybe. The DM can respond or choose not to answer. (500 GP)</item>
        <item name="the_nit_picker">Physical Description: Resembles a miniature garden gnome that carries lock picking tools in his hands. When not in use, looks like a 4" inch tall statue.

            Use: Twice daily, can be placed in front of a locked object to unlock it (functions as the spell “Knock”). At this point, the statue comes to life in order to pick the lock. After the lock is picked (or if he is unable to open it), reverts back to an inanimate statue.

            Side Effects: While picking the lock, the Nit Picker critiques any or all members of the party on their recent performance in the campaign. Nothing escapes the critical eye of the Nit Picker, no matter how small the perceived offense. (900 GP)</item>
        <item name="plastic_sheriff_badge">Adds +3 to bluff checks when impersonating a person of authority. (500 GP)</item>
        <item name="flaming_poisoning_raging_sword_of_doom">A sword with a gigantic blade, wreathed in flames and with a crooked, oozing scorpion’s stinger affixed to its point. Deals an extra 20 melee damage. (60000 GP)</item>
        <item name="no_sodium_salt_shaker">this might look like a simple salt shaker, but the contents have been bewitched to turn a bright shade of pink if sprinkled over food or drink that contains poison! (400 GP)</item>
        <item name="the_immovable_rod">Immovable Rod: This rod is a flat iron bar with a small button on one end. When the button is pushed (a move action), the rod does not move from where it is, even if staying in place defies gravity. Thus, the owner can lift or place the rod wherever he wishes, push the button, and let go. Several immovable rods can even make a ladder when used together (although only two are needed). An immovable rod can support up to 8,000 pounds before falling to the ground. If a creature pushes against an immovable rod, it must make a DC 30 Strength check to move the rod up to 10 feet in a single round. (1100 GP)</item>
        <item name="diadem_of_fabulous_truthiness">Once per long rest, you can channel your terminal fabulousity into this simple circlet and cast a free Zone of Truth, limited to a single target rather than a radius. Confound your enemies, emasculate your friends, and free up your cleric’s spell slots so he can do some actual healing. (900 GP)</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>

</resources>
